It is the turbulent Sengoku period.
어지러운 전국 시대.
Warlords keep on fighting day and night over Jipangu State, where Karakuri people live.
카라쿠리인이 사는 지팡구국에서는 군웅할거하여 밤낮으로 접전이 계속되고
Karakuri martial artists were sharpening their swords, dreaming of victory and honor.
카라쿠리 무예가들도 승리와 영광을 꿈꾸며 맹렬히 싸우고 있었다.
And now, a wild hero has arrived, seeking to be the number one Karakuri martial artist!
그리고 지금, 카라쿠리 무예가 제일을 꿈꾸는 터무니없는 영웅이 탄생했다!
Musashi is here-dasu!
무사시 등장이오!
Karakuri Kengouden
카라쿠리 검호전: 무사시 로드
A man always dreams of the day
사내는 언제나 세계 한가운데서
in the center of the world to become
제일 강해질 날을
AH! AH! the strongest
아! 아! 꿈꿔라
Raise the sword of your heart high to the wide sky
마음의 칼을 넓은 하늘로 번쩍 쳐들어
Raise the curtain to the road of adventure
모험의 길의 막을 연다
A skilled swordsman roams on Jipangu State
지팡구국을 떠도는 검호
His name is Musashi, a Karakuri man
그 이름은 카라쿠리인 무사시
Go! Fight!
가라! 싸워라!
The sound of fierce duels
격렬한 승부의 소리는
makes life dazzling
눈부신 인생
Battles of yesterdays make you stronger today
싸웠던 어제보다도 오늘 강해진다
Martial Arts! Dual Blade Musashi
무예! 이도류 무사시
Tomorrow will be glorious
내일은 빛난다
The sound of fierce duels
격렬한 승부의 소리는
makes life dazzling
눈부신 인생
Fight the utmost with the stillness
싸우는 한껏 고요함과 함께
Martial Arts! Dual Blade Musashi
무예! 이도류 무사시
His eyes shined! Musashi!
미간이 반짝였다 무사시!!
For the king and the sacred sword to escape to a safe place, Musashi and others disguised themselves and headed to Nikko.
국왕과 성검을 안전한 곳에 탈출시키기 위해서 무사시 일행은 변장해서 닛코로 향했다.
But Musashi and others were attacked by Shingen's Track Driving Corps.
그러나 신겐의 궤도주행군단에 습격당한 무사시 일행.
But by the friendship power of Karakuri martial artists, even Shingen had to retreat.
그렇지만 카라쿠리 무예가의 우정 파워로 대단한 신겐도 물러나고 말았다.
The Wooden Horse
목마는 무서운
was a Trap
함정이었소
Did Shingen fail too?
신겐도 실패했는가.
Return to Babel 13 right now.
즉시 출정해라. 바벨 13에 돌아와라.
What is the reason behind that?
그건 다시 어떤 이유로.
Don't try to deceive me. Megaton Castle is already destroyed to the extent that moving is all it can.
가만 넘어갈 생각 마라. 메가톤성의 파손, 이미 움직이는 게 고작일 뿐.
We're planning to attack as soon as the repair gets complete.
현재 서둘러 수리를 완료하는 대로 즉시 공격할 생각입니다.
You fool! Do you want Megaton Castle destroyed?
멍청한 자식. 메가톤성을 파괴할 생각이냐.
I won't say this again. REturn.
몇 번이고 말하지만, 귀환해라.
I cannot entrust this to you anymore.
이제 너희들에게는 맡길 수 없다.
Yessir!
예!
Everything is almost packed.
곧 짐싸기가 완료됩니다.
Great. The sea is calm, and we'll have a good sea voyage.
그래. 바다는 평온하니 좋은 항해가 되겠어.
Huh? What's that?
어? 저건?
That must be the monster raged at Edotopia.
틀림없이 에도토피아에서 날뛴 괴물이군.
I can't let that pass by.
보고 넘어갈 수는 없지.
Let Mr. Musashi know about this!
무사시 님에게 연락을!
Yessir!
예!
I'm bored...
심심하다...
I'm hungry again-dasu.
나 또 배고프오.
Hey! Stop slacking!
어이! 게으름 피우지 마라!
Y- yessir!
예, 예!
Oh, it's you, Kojirō-dasu. Please don't surprise us like that-dasu!
뭣이오, 코지로이오. 놀래키지 마시오.
Musashi, follow me.
무사시, 잠깐.
What is it-dasu?
뭣이오?
I wonder what're they talking about.
뭔 이야기일까?
What? We're chasing Megaton Castle from now on-dasu?
어? 지금부터 메가손을 쫒소?
Yes. I want to recover the shield and the jewel for the Highness as soon as possible.
그래. 국왕 전하를 위해 방패와 곡옥을 하루라도 빨리 되찾아 드리고 싶어.
I can't-dasu. I promised to meet Otsuru in 6 o'clock-dasu. Let's do that tomorrow-dasu.
나, 안 되오. 6시에 오츠루하고 만나기로 약속했소. 내일 하오.
We're going right now!
지금 당장 갈 거야!
I made an oath to myself to protect the throne of the Highness!
나, 전하의 왕좌를 꼭 지켜드리기로 맹세했어!
Can't you hear me, Musashi?!
내가 말하는 거 안 들리냐, 무사시!
No, but still...
아니, 그런 소릴 해도...
But, Senhime, this is too dangerous. Lord Ieyasu will not forgive us.
그래도, 센히메 님. 이건 너무 위험합니다. 이에야스 님이 용서시지 않을 겁니다.
Hey, it's still dangerous to be here. They'll come attack anyway!
어라, 위험한 건 여기 있어도 마찬가지잖아? 놈들 분명 덤벼올 거야!
But...
그래도...
Huh?
어?
What's wrong?
왜 그래?
What's that?
뭣이오.
Huh?
어?
That's light communication from Mr. Ryoma!
저건! 료마 님의 광통신!
Mr. Ryoma?
어? 료마 씨가?
What's he saying-dasu?
뭐라 하오?
I witnessed Megaton Castle at the harbor.
항구에서 메가톤성을 목격했다.
Megaton Castle! What a good timing! We must hurry!
메가톤성! 굿 타이밍이잖아! 서둘러야 해!
No! Unless Lord Ieyasu allows us to, I can't follow you!
안 됩니다! 이에야스 님의 허가를 받지 않으면 저는 함께 가지 않습니다!
I have Otsuru too...
나도 오츠루...
Megaton Castle is disappearing again while you're saying that!
그런 소리 하다가 또 메가톤성이 어디엔가 가 버리잖아!
I'll tell Lord Ieyasu about this.
이에야스 님께는 내가 잘 말해 둘게.
Jiraiyan! Thank you! Please do so!
지라이얀! 땡큐! 부탁해!
But...
그래도...
Oh, alright, Kojirō, you don't have follow me. You're fine with me being endangered, right?
그래, 괜찮아, 코지로는 안 와도. 내가 위험에 처해도 된단 거네?
That's why I'm stopping you!
그러니까, 저는 막고 있잖아요!
Let's go, Musashi!
가자, 무사시!
Jiraiyan, tell Otsuru that I can't make it by six today-dasu!
지라이얀, 오츠루한테 6시에 못 가게 된다고 말해 주시오!
Got it!
알았다!
Well.
어쩔 수 없나.
Princess!
공주님!
Mr. Musashi! This way!
무사시 님, 여기야!
Mr. Ryoma! Thank you for letting us know-dasu!
료마 씨! 알려 주셔서 고맙소!
Good to know that I helped you.
도움이 되어서 다행이야.
So, where did the monster head to?
그래서 괴물의 진로는?
It headed to west.
틀림없이 서쪽으로 향했다.
Then it must be heading to Seto Inland Sea.
그럼 분명 세토 내해로 가고 있겠군요.
Anyway, thank you for letting us ride, Mr. Ryoma.
어쨌든 잘 부탁드립니다, 료마 씨.
Irohamaru is heading to Seto Inland Sea, too. Leave it to me.
이로하마루의 목적지도 세토 내해. 맡겨 둬라.
Depart! Unfurl the sail!
출항! 돛을 올려라!
Otsuru! See you later-dasu!
오츠루! 갔다 오겠소!
Your Highness, I will take the shield and the jewel back for you.
국왕 전하, 방패와 곡옥은 제가 반드시 되찾겠습니다.
What is it, Hanzō?
뭔 일이냐, 한조.
Dokuganryu. Wouldn't you want to stop Megaton Castle?
도쿠간류. 메가톤성을 멈춰주지 않겠나.
What? Why?
뭐? 왜?
It's obvious. We'll go back and take the life of the king and the sacred sword.
뻔한 일을. 지금 되돌아가서 국왕의 목숨과 성검을 빼앗는 것이다.
But you should be knowing what will happen if you act against the order of Lord Rikudomaoh.
그러나 육도마왕 님의 명령에 거역하면 어떻게 되는지는 너도 알고 있을 터.
Hmph. They won't come to attack Megaton Castle anyway.
흥. 어차피 메가톤성에 공격을 하러 오진 못할 것이다.
Captain Dokuganryu! Please come back to the control room immediately! A suspicious ship is following us!
도쿠간류 함장님! 바로 조종실로 돌아와 주십시오! 수상한 배가 추적하고 있습니다.
That must be Irohamaru of some guy called Ryoma.
저건 분명 료마인가 하는 놈의 이로하마루.
I knew it. Those brats.
흥. 역시 저 꼬맹이들인가.
Prepare to attack!
공격 준비!
What's that-dasu?
뭣이오?
What's wrong, Musashi?
왜 그러냐, 무사시?
Something weird is heading towards the ship quickly-dasu.
이상한 게 대단한 속도로 여기로 오고 있소.
Something weird?
이상한 거라고?
Torpedos!
어뢰다!
What should we do, what should we do?!
아! 어째, 어째!
Turn big to right!
우현으로 크게!
Is it over?
지나갔나...
No, not yet.
아니, 아직이다.
He's right! It's coming again-dasu!
정말이오! 또 오오!
Turn big to left! Evade!
좌현으로 크게! 피해라!
Damn!
젠장!
We'll be hit-dasu!
당하오!
Mr. Musashi!
무사시 씨!
Jiraiyan! Ms. Otsuru, too!
지라이얀! 오츠루 님도!
Otsuru!
오츠루!
Kerokichi! Do it!
케로키치! 해라!
Captain! The torpedoes have changed their routes and are returning fast!
함장님! 어뢰가 진로를 바꾸어 급속으로 접근하고 있습니다!
Intercept!
요격해라!
It's impossible! There's not enough time!
불가능합니다! 시간이 부족합니다!
Thrust 20% decreased! The 4th floor bulkhead is wrecked! 500L of water is coming in every second!
추력 20% 저하! 제 4층 격벽 대파! 초당 500L씩 침수되고 있습니다!
It can't be helped! Cease firing and take emergency measures to respective places!
어쩔 수 없다! 전선 이탈! 침수 각소의 응급 조치를 서둘러라!
Hmph.
흥.
Otsuru! What's up-dasu?
오츠루! 뭔 일이오!
I was worried, you know.
그러니까, 걱정스럽잖아.
Here's your dangos!
여기, 단고!
I'm so happy that you brought dangos for me-dasu!
날 위해서 단고를 가져와 주다니 행복하오!
Mr. Musashi, I'd like to go with you.
무사시 씨, 나도 같이 갈래.
You can't fight when you're hungry!
그러니까, 배고프면 못 싸우잖아?
Otsuru!
오츠루!
Moreover, Kerokichi brought dango stand, too!
게다가, 케로키치 군이 단고 판매대도 옮겨 줬어! 그러니까 매일 얼마든지 단고 만들어 줄 수 있어. 모두 먹을 수 있고!
That's good to know!
오, 그거 좋네!
I disagree.
난 반대야.
We have an important mission. What if something happens to that girl if she goes with us?
우리는 중요한 임무가 있어. 여자얘를 데려가서 뭔 일이 있으면 어떻게 하게?
I'll protect her when that happens-dasu. It won't bother you-dasu!
그 때는 내가 지키오. 오센짱에게 피해는 안 끼치오!
You can't destroy Megaton Castle with that kind of way of thinking.
그런 순진한 사고방식으로는 메가톤성을 못 부숴.
But...
그래도...
Anyway, no!
어쨌든 안 돼!
Are you okay, Mr. Musashi?
무사시 씨, 괜찮아?
Now, let's continue tracking Megaton Castle!
자, 메가톤성 추적을 계속하자!
Y- yes...
네, 네...
Otsuru, don't feel down-dasu. I'll ask Osenchan later on again-dasu.
오츠루, 실망하지 마시오. 나, 나중에 오센짱한테 다시 한번 부탁해 보오.
Musashi! What are you doing?!
무사시! 뭐 해!
Got it-dasu! Later.
알겠소! 그럼 이따가.
This is weird-dasu. Even for Megaton Castle, it should have received fair amount of damage by the torpedoes...
이상하오. 아무리 메가톤성이라고 아까 어뢰로 상당히 피해를 입었을 텐데...
I can't see its shadow or its form-dasu.
그림자도 모습도 안 보이오.
It must be deep in the sea.
분명 바닷속 깊히 잠수했을 거야.
Considering that it appears around Seto Inland Sea, their hideout must be around here somewhere.
세토 내해에 출몰한다는 소문을 생각하면, 이 주변 어딘가에 놈들의 비밀 기지가 있을 지도 몰라.
Mr. Ryoma, can you lend us a small ship and a sub? I'd like to investigate the seabed with Musashi.
료마 님, 작은 배와 잠수함을 빌려주지 않으시겠습니까. 무사시와 둘이서 해저를 조사하겠습니다.
But there's a rumor that the monster swallows fisher boats. It's too dangerous.
그래도 그 괴물은 어선을 집어삼킨다는 소문이 있지. 위험해.
I am well aware of the dangers. Musashi.
원래부터 위험은 알고 있었습니다. 무사시.
Understood-dasu.
알겠소.
All right. If you're prepared for anything, then I'll happily lend those to you.
알겠다. 그렇게까지 말한다면 기쁘게 빌려 주지.
How incompetent of you, to bring an unnecessary present.
여기까지 선물을 데리고 오다니 정말 불미스럽군.
I apologize for that, but they're nothing more than jumping into their own disaster. We'll finish them at once.
죄송합니다만 놈들이야말로 스스로 재앙 속에 뛰어드는 놈들입니다. 반드시 단숨에 끝내주겠습니다.
You're saying big, but are you absolutely sure about that?
큰 소리를 해놓고 단언할 수 있겠나!
We brought them for an ingenious scheme. Please listen to us for now.
놈들을 끌고 온 건 묘책을 위함입니다. 먼저 들어 주십시오.
Musashi and others have entered Seto Inland sea. But a fearful trap is waiting in front of them.
세토 내해에 들어선 무사시 일행. 그러나 그 앞에 기다리는 것은 무서운 함정.
What will happen to them? Wait for the stormy latter half!
무사시 일행은 대체 어떻게 되는가? 질풍노도의 후반을 기다려라!
Karakuri Kengouden: Musashi Road
카라쿠리 검호전 무사시 로드
Great. Musashi and Kojirō are looking for stupid places. Use this chance to capture Senhime per our plan.
좋아. 무사시 일행이 엉뚱한 곳을 찾고 있다. 이 틈에 작전대로 센히메를 잡아라.
Yessir. But what if Senhime doesn't get off the ship?
예. 그러나 만약 센히메가 섬에 내리지 않는다면 어찌.
That restive horse cannot possibly stay on the ship.
그 날뛰는 말이라면 가만히 배 위에 있을 리가 없다.
I'm bored. Maybe I should have gone with Musashi.
아, 심심하다. 나도 무사시하고 같이 갈걸.
How thoughtful of you.
그러긴 미안한데.
I want to make a food for everyone that will cheer them up. Please let me cook dinner this time.
아니요, 오늘 밤만이라도 모두의 기운을 북돋아 주는 요리를 만들고 싶어요. 저도 모두의 저녁을 만들기 해 주세요.
Then, please do so!
그럼 부탁할게.
Great! I'll go get water!
네! 그럼 저 물 떠 올게요!
Otsuru!
오츠루!
Can I help you with gathering water?
물 뜨는거 도와줄까?
-Huh? -Two is always better, right?
-어? -혼자선 힘들잖아? 그치?
Let's make food for them today!
오늘은 대접하자!
I'm fine without you. I'll do it alone.
됐습니다. 혼자서 할게요.
I knew that she would refuse...
역시 거부당했네...
Senhime must be hating me. She's trying to celebrate my leave.
센히메 님, 날 싫어하는 거야. 날 쫒아내는 걸로 축하하는 것일 거야.
But could it not be it? Maybe I'm misunderstanding...
그래도 아닌 걸까. 설마 나...
No, that's obvious. Or she wouldn't be playing with Musashi all the time whenever I'm in front of them.
아니, 그게 당연해. 그게 아니면 맨날맨날 내 앞에서 무사시 씨하고 그렇게 사이좋게 놀 리가 없어.
I won't lose no matter what.
나, 절대 안 질 거야.
What a pure spring!
맑은 샘이구나!
It's cold!
차가워!
How awesome.
멋지다.
You don't have to follow me, really!
정말 괜찮다니까, 안 따라와도.
Mr. Ryoma's going to scold us if we don't!
아니, 료마 님께 혼납니다.
At this rate, I won't be able to talk with Otsuru at ease!
애고, 이래서는 오츠루 따라가도 느긋히 이야기할 수가 없잖아!
Help me!
살려줘!
Otsuru!
오츠루!
Senhime!
센히메 님!
What's this?
뭐야?
Mr. Musashi!
무사시 씨!
Stop!
멈춰!
Otsuru!
오츠루!
Senhime!
센히메 님!
Senhime! Leave this to us!
센히메 님! 저희에게 맡기세요!
Senhime! Run away!
센히메 님! 도망쳐요!
Put Otsuru down!
오츠루를 놔!
Senhime!
센히메 님!
Senhime! You can stop it now!
센히메 님! 이제 그만둬요!
Hey, wait a moment. I think we got a wrong girl in the trap. Isn't that Senhime instead?
어이, 잠깐만. 함정에 걸린 건 다른 여자잖아. 저게 센히메 아니야?
You mean that girl covered in mud?
저 흙투성이 여자 말이야?
I can't really distinguish from this description, but you might be true.
이 인상서로는 잘 모르겠는데 그럴지도 모르겠구먼.
We might have ended up being scolded by Lord Hanzō!
이래선 한조 님께 혼이라도 날 틈이었군!
What are you doing?! Let me go!
뭔 짓이야! 놔!
Senhime!
센히메 님!
Stop!
멈춰!
Otsuru!
오츠루!
Mr. Musashi!
무사시 씨!
Otsuru, are you injured-dasu?
오츠루, 상처는 없소?
Mr. Musashi! Senhime... Senhime was...
무사시 씨! 센히메 님이! 센히메 님이!
Otsuru, It's not your fault-dasu!
오츠루 잘못이 아니오.
I- I was wrong.
내, 내가 잘못한 거야.
So, what did they say?
그래서 놈들이 뭐라?
They left this letter.
이 편지를 남기고 갔어.
(hour of rooster: 5:00~7:00 PM)
무사시에게 코지로에게 전한다. 센히메를 구하고 싶으면 오늘 밤 유시에 둘이서만 센죠곡에 올 것. 한조.
He always uses dirty tricks-dasu!
매번이고 더러운 수만 쓰는 놈이오!
Senhime!
센히메 님!
Otsuru, it'll be all right-dasu! I'll rescue Osenchan no matter what!
오츠루, 괜찮소! 오센짱은 꼭 구해낼 테니까!
Mr. Musashi...
무사시 씨...
That Hanzō is unforgivable-dasu!
한조 놈, 용서할 수 없소!
Under that cliff is Senjo Valley.
저 낭떠러지 아래가 센죠곡이다.
So deep-dasu...
깊소...
It's almost time.
슬슬 시각이다.
What's that-dasu?
뭣이오?
Osenchan!
오센짱!
Senhime!
센히메 님!
Stop-dasu!
멈추시오!
Be careful, Musashi!
조심해라, 무사시!
Of course-dasu!
알겠소!
Stop-dasu!
멈추시오!
Damn!
젠장!
Musashi!
무사시!
You've fallen into my trap.
감쪽같이 함정에 걸려들었구나.
You always act like fools!
언제나 바보같은 놈들이여!
We already knew that this was a trap! Now, let Senhime go!
함정이란 건 알고 왔다! 센히메를 놓아라!
You can rescue her from the wooden horse by yourselves. If you survive, that is.
목마에서는 너희가 알아서 구해주면 된다. 살아남는다면 말이지.
-Let's go, Musashi! -Right!
-가자, 무사시! -좋소!
What's that-dasu?
뭣이오?
I forgot to tell you that mines are all over that village. Be careful!
말하는 걸 잊어먹었는데, 그 골짜기에는 무수히 많은 지뢰가 널려 있으니 힘껏 주의해라!
Damn!
젠장!
Mr. Musashi...
무사시 씨...
Judging from your story, the wooden horse should be being controlled by someone nearby.
이야기에서 듣자하니, 목마는 누군가 가까이서 조종당하고 있을 터.
Around this place...
분명 이 주변에...
Over there!
저기!
Huh?
어?
It seems that our job is over.
아무래도 우리 일도 끝난 것 같구나.
Alright! Move the wooden horse to here!
좋아, 목마를 여기로 유도해라!
Yessir! Huh?
예! 어?
Damn!
젠장!
Senhime!
센히메 님!
Otsuru! Where is Musashi and Kojirō?
오츠루! 무사시하고 코지로는?
They fell into a trap...
그게, 함정에 빠져서...
Get on, Otsuru.
타, 오츠루.
Yes!
네!
Hey, you two! It's dangerous!
아, 둘 다! 위험해!
Alright, let's go!
좋아, 가자!
Hey, stop!
어이, 관둬!
Of course, they won't listen.
이라고 말해서 들을 리가 없지.
Kojirō!
코지로!
I'm fine.
괜찮다.
It's time for you to be punished. You'd better fall onto the mine surface and smashed to small fragments.
슬슬 처벌받을 때가 왔구나. 지뢰면에 떨어져서 산산조각이나 나라.
Damn!
젠장!
Musashi!
무사시!
Damn! They approached?
젠장, 다가왔냐!
Don't come! It's dangerous here-dasu!
오지 마시오! 위험하오!
Senhime!
센히메 님!
Mr. Musashi!
무사시 씨!
Musashi!
무사시!
Get on!
올라타!
Hothothothot! Damn, this again! Remember this!
뜨거뜨거뜨거뜨거! 젠장! 또! 기억해 두어라!
Thank you, Otsuru.
오츠루, 고마워.
Senhime, I'm sorry. I thought wrongly of you...
센히메 님. 죄송해요. 저, 센히메 님을...
It's alright. You rescued me, you know.
괜찮다니까. 게다가 오츠루가 구해 줬잖아.
Please keep helping like this.
지금부터도 잘 부탁해.
Yes! Does that mean I can stay together?
네! 그럼 같이 있어도 좋아요?
Of course. With our power combined, we might not need Musashi at all!
물론이야. 둘이서 힘을 모으면 무사시 따위 필요하지 않을지도!
Wait! You shouldn't looking down of them-dasu! You're safe because I'm here!
잠깐! 둘 다 놈들을 쉽게 보면 안 되오! 내가 있으니까!
I know that, you silly! Let's combine all our powers and do our best!
안다니까. 다들 힘을 모아서 힘내자!
A crisis is gone, thanks to the victory of teamwork.
팀워크의 승리로 위기는 넘겼다. 그러나 다시 메가톤성을 쫒아 방패와 곡옥을 되찾아야만 하는 무사시 일행.
Thanks to the smile of reconciliation between Senhime and Otsuru, Musashi was burning with a new determination.
센히메와 오츠루의 화해의 미소에 기운이 난 무사시는 새로운 결의로 불타오르고 있엇다.
I fought and I got beaten
싸우고 맞았어
Nosebleed drips rendezvous
코피 쓩이야 랑데부
I can't lose, so take my blow!
나도 지지 않으려 한발!
Pinch! Punch! I won by reversal
핀치 펀치로 대역전
Next is delightful lunchtime
다음 시간 즐거운
But it's not delightful today
급식일 텐데
The thunder of my teacher
선생님의 벼락이
only hit me and nobody else
나한테만 떨어져 왔어
I tried to explain
사정을 말해도
But he won't listen
들어주지 않는 채
Now whatever I do
어떻게 해도 역시
I end up crying
눈물이 나오고 말아
Don't cry when you eat, or
울면서 밥먹으면
it tastes totally bad
완전 맛없어
you'll feel downhearted
왠지 안타까워
We're doing everything we can to discover the base of Rikudomaoh-dasu!
육도마왕의 본거지를 찾기 위해 우리는 필사적이오! 거기서 주베 씨의 밀정이 정보를 가지고 왔소.
The true identity of Rikudomaoh is Nobunaga-dasu! But then Shingen appeared again!
무슨, 육도마왕의 정체는 노부나가였소! 그 때 다시 신겐이!
In addition, Kenshin appeared and they combined-dasu!
덤으로 켄신까지 달려들어 합체하오!
We're in big crisis-dasu!
우리는 큰 위기에 처했소!
Next story! Shingenshin of Sky and Ground
다음 이야기! 하늘과 땅의 신겐신이오
It's the stormy Seto Inland Sea-dasu!
질풍노도의 세토 내해이오!
Next Episode
다음 이야기
Shingenshin
하늘과 땅의
of Sky and Ground
신겐신이오
Look forwards for it!
기대하세요!